Take me there there there there there there there
Take me there there there there there there
Take me there
Can we go far away
to a room with a view
You can take me anywhere
just as long as I'm with you
Take me there there there there there there there
Take me there there there there there there
Take me anywhere
Take me there
Take me there there there there there there there
Take me there there there there there there
Can we go far far away
to a room with a view
You can take me anywhere
just as long as I'm with you
Leave a life where dreams come true
In a world that lets you breathe
You can take me anywhere
Just as long as you're with me
Take me there there there there there there there
Take me there there there there there there
Take me
Take me there
There there there there there there
Dreams come true with you